http://www.ivyessays.com/privacy.asp

Ivy Essays: Professional editing services and essay sales for business school, law school, medical school, and undergraduate applicants
buy essays
editing services
free essay tips and advice
by school  |  by work experience  |  by applicant backgroundorder formgeneral tips  |  topic selection  |  creating structure  |  leads and ends  |  writing the essay  |  final touches  |  funny mistakesbuy essays
editing services
free essay tips and advice
by background/interest  |  by school rank  |  by questionorder formgeneral tips  |  topic selection  |  creating structure  |  leads and ends  |  writing the essay  |  final touches  |  funny mistakesbuy essays
editing services
free essay tips and advice
order formgeneral tips  |  topic selection  |  creating structure  |  leads and ends  |  writing the essay  |  final touches  |  funny mistakesbuy essays
editing services
free essay tips and advice
order formgeneral tips  |  topic selection  |  creating structure  |  leads and ends  |  writing the essay  |  final touches  |  funny mistakesediting services
order form
0 items $ 0
Got writer?s block? Need inspiration?
Choose from thousands of sample essays written by applicants who got in!
click here
Want a 2nd Opinion?
Need a full grammatical review?
Put our professional editors to work for you!
click here
Home > Privacy Policy
Introduction
IvyEssays
respects each individual’s right to personal privacy.
We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.
Information Collection
IvyEssays collects information through our order form and through automatic logging files through our web host.
Cookies are utilized by IvyEssays.com. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive. Cookies enable IvyEssays.com to track purchase information and who referred customers to our site.
It is important for us to find out how our customers hear about us in order for us to advertise effectively. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.
Information Usage
The information collected by IvyEssays.com through our order form is used for credit card verification and to help us determine where our customers heard about us in order to hone our marketing efforts.
Information collected through log files informs us (on a group basis) of our customers’ browser types, operating systems, click stream activity and some demographic information.
This information is pooled - collecting no personal information. It allows us to customize our Web site in order to provide the best user experience for our customers.
Personal information such as names and email addresses is not used for marketing practices.
Only demographic information is utilized for these efforts.
IvyEssays.com NEVER shares our customers’ information with other parties.
Information contained in the essays that our customers submit for editing services is only read by the editor assigned to each customer.
That information is never shared and is never stored.
Essays submitted to IvyEssays for editing services are never used in any way except to provide editing services to the client.
When a customer sells us the rights to use and resell their essays, all personal information contained in the essays is removed by IvyEssays and/or the customer before the essays are shown to any 3rd party.
Once these essays are sold to IvyEssays.com and release forms have been signed by the client, the essays become the sole property of IvyEssays.com.
Problem Resolution
If problems arise, users may contact us by email.
We are committed to resolving disputes within 3 business days.
Data Storage and Security
IvyEssays.com protects user information by utilizing secure servers and SSL encryption.
If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us.
Home  |  Editing Services  |  Buy Essays  |  Shopping Cart  |  About Us  |  Contact UsSell Essays  |  Samples of our work  |  Testimonials  |  Privacy Policy© Copyright 1996-2006, IvyEssays. All rights reserved.
